我好想念茱莉
Man, I sure miss Julie.
西班牙侏儒
Spanish midgets.
西班牙侏儒摔角…
Spanish midgets wrestling...
茱莉 好 是的 我懂你为何会这样联想
Julie. Okay, yes, I see how you got there.
你搞清楚了那玩意的用途吗？
You ever figure out what that thing's for?
不 是这样的 我在试着过滤电话
No, see, I'm trying this screening thing.
我认为我老是接电话 人们会觉得我生活贫乏
I figure if I always answer the phone, people will think I don't have a life.
我的天 罗德里哥从来不会被压制
My God. Rodrigo never gets pinned.
哔声要来了 你知道该怎么做
Here comes the beep. You know what to do.
你好 我要找巴伯
Hello. I'm looking for Bob.
我是洁德
This is Jade.
我不知道你是否还用这号码 但我只是想到彼此
I don't know if you're still at this number, but I was just thinking about us...
和以前有多棒 我知道那已是三年前的事 但…
and how great it was, and, well, I know it's been three years...
我有点希望我们再次接头
but I was kind of hoping we could hook up again.
你知道吗？ 我几乎没勇气打这通电话
You know, I barely had the nerve to make this call...
- 所以你知道我做了什么吗？ - 什么？
- so you know what I did?     - What?
我喝得微醺
I got a little drunk...
还全身赤裸
and naked.
我是巴伯
Bob here.
没有人告诉你活着有多累
∮ So no one told you life was gonna be this way ∮
上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘
∮ Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. ∮
寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累
∮ It's like you're always stuck in second gear ∮
日复一日 年复一年
∮ When it hasn't been your day, ∮
时运不济 活着受罪
∮ your week, your month, or even your year ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ but I'll be there for you ∮
纵有狂风暴雨
∮ When the rain starts to pour ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ I'll be there for you ∮
支持一如往昔
∮ Like I've been there before ∮
你我永不离弃
∮ I'll be there for you ∮
你我相偎相依
∮ 'Cause you're there for me too ∮
所以说… 你近况怎样？
So, uh, what have you been up to?
你知道的 跟平常一样
Oh, you know, the usual.
教有氧运动
Teaching aerobics...
玩得太过火
partying way too much. Heh.
假如你不确定…
Oh, and in case you were wondering...
新的詹姆士庞德电影海报上 是我的双腿
those are my legs on the new James Bond poster.
你能等一下吗？我有另一通电话
Can you hold on a moment? I have another call.
- 我爱她   - 我懂
- I love her.     - I know.
- 我回来了   - 我们要不要相聚？
- I'm back.     - So are we gonna get together?
当然好
Uh, absolutely.
明天下午怎么样？
Uh, how about tomorrow afternoon?
你知道村区的中央咖啡厅吗？五点左右怎样？
Do you know, uh, Central Perk in the village? Say, five-ish?
- 太好了 到时见   - 好
- Great. I'll see you then.     - Okay.
很好
Okay.
装电话终于值得了
Having a phone has finally paid off.
就算你模仿巴伯很像
Even though you do do a good Bob impression...
我想她明天见到你时
I'm thinking when she sees you tomorrow...
她大概会发现 嘿 你不是巴伯
she's probably gonna realize, hey, you're not Bob.
我希望的是 当巴伯没出现时
I am hoping that when Bob doesn't show up...
她会向隔壁桌陌生人张开的双臂寻求慰藉
she will seek comfort in the open arms of the wry stranger at the next table.
我的天 你邪恶到极点
Oh, my God. You are pure evil.
好 邪恶到极点
Okay, pure evil...
欲望难耐又孤单
horny and alone.
我曾经这样过
I've done this.
对 大家都在这
Yeah, yeah, everybody's here.
嘿 大家 向在新墨西哥的茱莉说声嗨
Hey, everybody. Say hi to Julie in New Mexico.
嗨 茱莉
Hi, Julie.
好 趁着罗斯在讲电话
Okay. While Ross is on the phone...
大家欠我六十二元 用来庆祝他生日
everybody owes me 62 bucks for his birthday.
有没有可能你取个整数就好？
Um, is there any chance that you're rounding up from...
像是二十元？
you know, from like 20?
拜托 我们要买礼物 看演唱会和买蛋糕
Hey, come on, we got the gift, the concert and the cake.
我们需要蛋糕？
Do we need a cake?
听着 我知道金额有点高
Look, I know it's a little steep.
喔嘘
Whoosh.
不过是为了罗斯
But it's Ross.
- 对 是为了罗斯   - 你说得对
- Yeah, it's Ross.     - Yeah, you're right.
好吗？好 大家待会见 我必须去…
All right? Okay. I'll see you later. I gotta go...
做一件事
do a thing.
好 亲爱的 我今晚再打给你
Okay, sweetheart, I'll call you later tonight.
等等 你不会真的要这么做吧？
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey, you're not really going through with this, are you?
我想我也许会去做
You know, I think I might just.
那么你们今晚晚饭要做什么？
So, uh, what are you guys doing for dinner tonight?
我想我必须开始为罗斯的生日存钱
Well, I guess I gotta start saving up for Ross' birthday.
所以我可能会留在家里吃积尘
So I guess I'll just stay home and eat dust bunnies.
你们能相信这要花那么多钱吗？
Can you believe how much this is gonna cost?
你们有没有过这种感觉… ？
Do you guys ever get the feeling that, um...
钱德和他们几个…
Chandler and those guys...
不了解我们赚的钱不如他们多？
just don't get that we don't make as much money as they do?
- 对   - 真的？
- Yes.     - Really?
他们老是说"咱们去这里 去那里"
It's like they're always saying, "Let's go here, let's go there."
- 像是我们负担得起去这里和那里一样   - 对
- Like we can afford to go here and there.     - Yeah.
对 而且我们总是必须去 某个不错的地方
Yes, and we always have to go to, you know, someplace nice, you know?
我们没什么说话的余地 因为像这是为了生日
It's not like we can say anything about it, because, like, this is a birthday thing...
而且是为了罗斯
you know, and it's for Ross.
- 为了罗斯   - 为了罗斯
- For Ross.     - For Ross.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
- 嗨   - 怎么了？
- Hi.     - What?
是这样的 我在工作
Okay. I'm at work...
只是平凡的一天 切菜… 炒菜…
just an ordinary day, you know, chop, chop, sauté, sauté.
突然间经理里昂 叫我到他办公室
All of a sudden, Leon, the manager, calls me into his office.
原来他们开除了午餐主厨 猜猜谁得到那份工作？
Turns out they fired the head lunch chef, and guess who got the job.
假如不是你 这故事还真悲惨
If it's not you, this is a horrible story.
- 幸好是我   - 哦
- Fortunately, it is me.     - Oh.
而且他们升我为采购主管 多谢大家
And they made me head of purchasing, thank you very much.
真棒
That's so cool.
我刚刚在楼下碰到钱德和罗斯 我们应该出外庆祝
Anyway, I just ran into Chandler and Ross. We should go out and celebrate.
到某个不错的地方
You know, someplace nice.
- 不错的地方   - 对
- Someplace nice.     - Yeah.
你想我卖肾能赚多少钱？
How much you think I can get for my kidney?
(中央咖啡厅)
我告诉你 你不能这么做
I'm telling you, you can't do this.
拜托 我用普通方法绝对追不到那种女生
Oh, come on, I can't get a girl like that with conventional methods.
那不是重点
That doesn't matter.
她是要打电话给巴伯
She wanted to call Bob.
就我们所知 巴伯才应该跟她在一起
Hey, for all we know, Bob is who she was meant to be with.
你也许在破坏 两个人追求快乐的机会
You may be destroying two people's chance for happiness.
我们不认识巴伯
We don't know Bob.
好吗？我们认识我 我们喜欢我 拜托让我快乐
Okay? We know me. We like me. Please let me be happy.
过去那里 告诉那女人真相
Go over there and tell that woman the truth.
好吧
All right.
去
Go.
嗨
Hi.
听着 我必须…
Listen, I have to, uh, ahem...
我必须坦承一件事
I have to confess something.
什么事？
Yes?
放你鸽子的那个人是烂人
Whoever stood you up is a jerk.
- 你怎么… ？ - 我不知道
- How did you...     - I don't know.
我只是有种奇怪的感应 不过这就是我 我古怪而敏感
I just had this weird sense. You know? But that's me, I'm weird and sensitive.
要面纸吗？
Tissue?
谢了
Thanks.
不 你留着那包
No, no, you keep the pack.
我今天已经哭完了
I'm all cried out today.
好了…
Okay, okay.
现在来敬我妹 新上任的午餐主厨
Here is to my sister, the newly appointed head lunch chef.
而且还负责采购
Who is also in charge of purchasing.
新上任的午餐主厨 还负责采购
Newly appointed head lunch chef, also in charge of purchasing...
还有自己的小办公桌 假如罗兰不在场
Who has her own little desk when Roland's not there.
午餐主厨 采购 罗兰不在场时有自己的小办公桌
Uh, lunch chef, purchasing, own little desk when Roland's not there...
- 敬我的妹妹…    - 等等 我还收到呼叫器
- here's to my little sister...     - Oh, wait. And I got a beeper.
好酷
Oh, cool.
- 很好 我先等   - 对不起
- That's fine, I'll just wait.     - Aw, sorry.
对不起…
Oh, sorry, sorry.
敬摩妮卡
Monica.
大家准备点菜了吗？
Are we ready to order?
我们还没看菜单
Oh. You know, we haven't even looked yet.
你们看过后 请让我知道
Well, when you do, just let me know.
我会坐在我座位边边等候
I'll be right over there on the edge of my seat.
哇 看看这些价格
Wow, look at these prices.
是啊 真不得了
Yeah, these are pretty "cha-ching."
对啊 这些是什么 著名的鸡吗？
I know. What are these, famous chickens?
- 抱歉 我迟到了 摩妮卡 恭喜   - 谢了
- Sorry I'm late. Congratulations, Mon.     - Thanks.
我不为迟到感到抱歉 我跟洁德相处的下午超精彩
I'm not sorry I'm late. How incredible was my afternoon with Jade?
蛮精彩的 根据她在我答录机的留言可知
Well, pretty incredible, according to the message she left on my machine.
嘿 钱德 为什么这个女人在我的答录机留言给你？
Hey, Chandler, why is this woman leaving a message for you on my machine?
我必须告诉她 我的号码是你的号码
See, I had to tell her that my number was your number.
我不能告诉她我的号码是我的号码
I couldn't tell her my number was my number...
因为她以为我的号码是巴伯的号码
because she thinks my number is Bob's number.
再告诉我一次 当古板房东罗普打来 我该怎么做？
Hey, tell me again. What do I do when Mr. Roper calls?
我该大胆问一下吗？
Do I dare ask?
好 我开胃菜要生牛肉 然后主菜是烤明虾
Yes, I'll start with the carpaccio, and then I'll have the grilled prawns.
- 听起来很棒 我也一样   - 这位男士呢？
- That sounds great, same for me.     - And for the gentleman?
是 我点泰式鸡肉披萨
Yeah, I'll have the Thai chicken pizza.
但是 听着 假如我的不放坚果 韭葱等材料
But, hey, look, if I get it without the nuts and leeks and stuff...
会比较便宜吗？
is it cheaper?
你以为会 是不是？
You'd think, wouldn't you?
- 小姐？ - 好的
- Miss?     - Okay.
我要佐餐的沙拉
I will have the, uh... side salad.
它要佐什么餐？
And what would that be on the side of?
我不知道
I don't know.
你不如把它放在我的水旁边
Why don't you just put it right here next to my water?
那么你呢？
And for you?
我要一碗黄瓜汤
Um, I'm gonna have a cup of the cucumber soup...
以及…
and, um...
保重
take care.
- 我点纽奥良鱿鱼   - 还要别的吗？
- I will have the, uh, Cajun catfish.     - Anything else?
是 来唱一段《情歌销魂》怎样？
Yes, how about a verse of "Killing Me Softly"?
你会对我的鱼打喷嚏 是不是？
You're gonna sneeze in my fish, aren't you?
加上小费 除以六
Plus tip, divided by six...
好 每个人欠我二十八元
Okay, everyone owes 28 bucks.
每个人？
Um, everyone?
你说得对 真抱歉
Oh. You're right, I'm sorry.
谢谢
Thank you.
今晚是摩妮卡的大日子 她不该付钱
It's Monica's big night. She shouldn't pay.
谢谢
Aw, thank you.
所以我们五个人…
So five of us is...
各付三十三块半
33.50 apiece.
不 才不要 抱歉 不可能
No. Uh-uh. No way. Sorry, not gonna happen.
像是毕业舞会情景重演
Whoa. Whoa. Prom night flashback.
抱歉 摩妮卡 我真的很高兴你升迁
Sorry, Monica. I'm really happy you got promoted...
但是冷黄瓜糊要三十几元？
but cold cucumber mush for 30-something bucks?
不
No.
瑞秋只吃了一小份沙拉
Rachel just had that little salad...
乔伊则吃他的一小块彼萨
and Joey with his, like, teeny pizza.
好 菲比
Okay, Pheebs.
不如我们各付各的 好吗？
How about we'll each just pay for what we had, okay?
- 没什么大不了   - 对你是这样
- It's no big deal.     - Not for you.
好了 怎么回事？
All right, what's going on?
好吧 听着 我现在真的不想淌这浑水
Okay, look, I really don't wanna get into this right now.
- 这只会让大家都不舒服   - 好 没关系 好
- It'll just make everybody uncomfortable.     - Oh, fine. All right, fine.
- 干嘛？ - 你能告诉我们
- What? Whoa, whoa.     - You can tell us.
对 拜托 是我们 好吗？ 我们能接受
Yeah, hello? It's us. All right? We'll be fine.
是啊
Yeah.
唔 好的 恩
Ahem. Okay, um...
我们三个觉得…
Uh, we three feel like that, uh, ahem...
有时候你们不了解…
sometimes you guys don't get that, uh, ahem...
我们的钱不如你们多
We don't have as much money as you.
- 好   - 我听到了
- Okay.     - I hear you.
我们能讨论这件事
We can talk about that.
那么…
Well, then...
就来…
let's.
我猜我从没想到 钱会构成问题
Well, um, I guess I just never think of money as an issue.
- 因为你有钱   - 这一点说得好
- That's because you have it.     - That's a good point.
那么…  你们为何以前从没提过这件事？
So, um, how come you guys haven't talked about this before?
因为总是有事情发生 像是摩妮卡的新职位
Because it's always something, you know? Like with Monica's new job...
或是罗斯生日要盛大庆祝
or the whole Ross' birthday hoopla.
什么？嘿…
What? Whoa, hey.
我不希望我的生日 造成任何负面…
I don't want my birthday to be the source of any kind of negative...
到时候会有盛大庆祝？
There's gonna be a hoopla?
基本上有那玩意 然后还有那玩意后的事…
Basically there's the thing, and then the stuff after the thing and it's...
假如这会让大家好过些 我们可以别管那玩意
If it makes anybody feel better, we can just forget the thing...
只要送礼就好
and we'll just do the gift.
礼物？那玩意不是礼物？
Gift? The thing's not the gift?
不 那玩意是 我们要去看混混与自大狂合唱团
No, the thing was we were gonna go see Hootie and the Blowfish.
混混与… 我的天 我听广播就听得到他们的歌
Hootie and the... Oh, my... I can catch them on the radio.
不 现在我觉得内咎了 你想去参加演唱会
No. Now I feel bad. You wanna go to the concert.
不 听着 这是我生日
No, look, hey, it's my birthday...
最重要的是我们能一起欢庆
and the important thing is that we all be together.
- 我们所有人   - 在一起
- All of us.     - Together.
不是在演唱会场
Not at the concert.
- 好 谢谢   - 谢了
- Okay. Thank you.     - Thanks.
耶
Yeah.
所以说 伊波拉病毒 真要命吧？
So, the Ebola virus. That's gotta suck, huh?
天呀 摩妮卡 袋子里有什么？
Gee, Monica. What's in the bag?
我不知道 钱德 咱们来看看
I don't know, Chandler. Let's take a look.
像是短剧表演
Oh, it's like a skit.
原来是六人晚餐 五块牛排
Why, it's dinner for six. Five steaks...
和给菲比的一条茄子
and an eggplant for Phoebe.
我们工作地点换了肉类供应商 新商家给我牛排当谢礼
We switched meat suppliers at work, and they gave me the steaks as a thank-you.
但是等等 还有 钱德 那信封里有什么？
But wait, there's more. Hey, Chandler, what is in that envelope?
顺带一提 在走廊练习时好像没那么呆
By the way, this didn't seem so dorky out in the hall.
快点
Come on.
原来是混混与自大狂合唱团的六张门票
Why, it's six tickets to Hootie and the Blowfish.
自大狂
The Blowfish.
我们请客 好吗？所以别担心 由我们招待
It's on us, all right? So don't worry. This is our treat.
所以… 谢谢
So... thank you.
你们能更冷淡一点吗？
Could you be less enthused?
听着 这是很好的表示 真的
Look, it's a nice gesture. It is.
可是感觉就像…
But it just feels like...
像… ？
Like?
- 施舍   - 施舍？
- Charity.     - Charity?
我们只是想做好事
We're just trying to do a nice thing here.
但是 罗斯 你必须了解 你的好事令我们觉得好渺小
But, Ross, you have to understand, your nice thing makes us feel about this big.
其实是令我们觉得这么渺小
Actually, it makes us feel that big.
为什么？我不懂 我们好像怎么做 你们都觉得不对
What? I don't understand. I mean, it's like we can't win with you guys.
假如你们觉得这么渺小 也许那不是我们的错
If you guys feel this big, maybe that's not our fault.
也许那只是你们的感受
Maybe that's just how you feel.
噢
Oh.
- 你现在断定我们的感受   - 我们不该说起这件事的
- Now you're telling us how we feel.     - We never should have talked about this.
我要谢绝演唱会
I'm gonna pass on the concert...
因为我现在没心情听混混
because I'm just not in a very Hootie place right now.
- 我也一样   - 我也是
- Me neither.     - Me too.
各位 我们买了门票
Guys, we bought the tickets.
那么你们有额外座位 让你们放皇冠等等
Well, then you'll have extra seats, you know, for all your tiaras and stuff.
你说的时候为何看着我？
Why did you look at me when you said that?
所以我想我们不能去了
So I guess now we can't go.
拜托 你们想做什么就做 我们非得做什么都在一起吗？
Come on, do what you want. Do we always have to do everything together?
知道吗？你说得对
You know what? You're right.
- 好   - 好
- Fine.     - Fine.
- 好   - 好的
- Fine.     - All right.
我们要去了
We're gonna go.
还有六小时才开始 我们到时候再去
It's not for another six hours. We're gonna go then.
- 钱德？ - 在
- Chandler?     - Yeah.
天啊
Oh, jeez.
- 你准备好没？ - 好了
- Are you ready?     - Yes.
让我拿西装外套 跟你说我今天跟人上床了
Just let me grab my jacket and tell you I had sex today. Whoa, whoa.
什么？你今天跟人上床？
What? You had sex today?
由别人说这句话 听起来更酷
Wow. It sounds even cooler when somebody else says it.
我很厉害 好吗？ 她拼命咬着嘴唇 才不会尖叫出来
I was awesome, okay? She was biting her lip to stop from screaming.
哇噢
Wow.
我知道我有阵子没做了 但我把那当成好的迹象
Now, I know it's been a while, but I took that as a good sign.
还在过滤电话？
Still doing the screening thing?
我今天跟人上床了
I had sex today.
我永远不必再接电话了
I never have to answer that phone again.
哔声要来了 你知道该怎么做
Here comes the beep. You know what to do.
嘿 巴伯 是我洁德 听着…
Hey, Bob. It's Jade.
我只想告诉你 你前几天没出现 令我好受伤
I just wanted to tell you I was really hurt when you didn't show up the other day.
所以告诉你 我最后认识了一个男的
And just so you know, I ended up meeting a guy.
我是巴伯
Bob here.
喔 嗨
Oh, hi.
你认识了别人吗？
So, uh, you met someone, huh?
是的 我认识了别人
Yes. Yes, I did.
事实上 我两小时前跟他上了床
In fact, I had sex with him two hours ago.
那么他表现怎样？
So, uh, how was he?
呃…
Eh...
呃？
"Eh"?
巴伯 他根本比不上你
Oh, Bob, he was nothing compared to you.
我必须咬着嘴唇 才不会叫出你的名字
I had to bite my lip to keep from screaming your name.
那令我真欣慰
Well, that makes me feel so good.
过程很笨拙又颠簸
It was just so awkward and bumpy.
颠簸？
Bumpy?
也许他有某种很酷的新风格 只是你不熟悉
Maybe he had some kind of, uh, new cool style that you're not familiar with.
也许你只要习惯就好
And, uh, maybe you have to get used to it.
没多少时间能让我习惯 你懂我意思吧？
There wasn't much time to get used to it... ...if you know what I mean.
你知道吗？我没办法乐在其中
You know what? I'm not gonna be able to enjoy this.
对 我懂 这是我生日 我们应该全都在场
Yeah, I know. It's my birthday. We all should be here.
那么走吧
So let's go.
也许我们该留下来听一首歌
Well, you know, maybe we should stay for one song.
对 假如我们现在离开 对他们很没礼貌
Yeah, I mean, it would be rude to them for us to leave now.
再说 他们可能也过得很高兴
You know, the guys are probably having a great time.
拜托 两位 再一次
Come on, you guys. One more time.
好的
Okay.
不是
No.
谢谢大家 我们是混混与自大狂
Thank you very much. We are Hootie & The Blowfish.
- 好精彩   - 太棒了
- That was amazing.     - Excellent.
我不敢相信他们错过这场
I can't believe the guys missed this.
什么人？喔 对了
What guys? Oh, yeah.
打扰一下 你是摩妮卡·盖勒吗？
Excuse me. You're Monica Geller, aren't you?
- 我认识你吗？ - 你以前是我的保姆
- Do I know you?     - You used to be my baby-sitter.
我的天 小史提夫·费雪？
Oh, my God. Little Stevie Fisher?
你近来好吗？
How have you been?
很好 我现在是律师
Good, good. I'm a lawyer now.
你不可能是律师 你才八岁
You can't be a lawyer. You're 8.
听着 很高兴见到你 我得回后台了
Well, listen, it was nice to see you. I gotta run backstage.
- 等等 后台？ - 对 我的事务所代表这乐团
- Wait, backstage?     - Oh, yeah. My firm represents the band.
- 罗斯   - 钱德
- Ross.     - Chandler.
- 你们想跟乐团见面吗？ - 对 我们想
- Look, you guys wanna meet the group?     - Yeah, we do.
来吧
Come on.
听着 你是跟我爸乱搞的保姆之一吗？
So, look, are you one of the ones that fooled around with my dad?
- 你们好   - 生日快乐
- Hey, you guys.     - Happy birthday.
谢谢…
Oh, thank you. Thanks.
所以…
So, uh...
你们昨晚过得怎样？
How was your night last night?
蛮逊的 那么你们呢？
Oh, well, it pretty much sucked. How was yours?
我们的也很逊
Yeah, ours pretty much sucked too.
但是我遇到小史提夫·费雪 记得他吗？
Oh, but I did run into Stevie Fisher. Remember him?
对 我以前当过他保姆
Oh, yeah. I used to baby-sit him.
他爸还好吗？
Hey, how's his dad?
很好
Good.
除此之外 整个晚上实在没什么好提的
Uh, aside from that, the whole evening was pretty much a bust.
对 我们很想你们
Yeah, we really missed you guys.
听着 我们想说 这整件事真是太傻了
Yeah, look, we were just saying, this whole thing is so stupid.
我们必须真的不让金钱之类的事 影响到…
We just have to really, really not let stuff like money, get like...
那是草莓吗？
Is that a hickey?
不 我只是…
Oh, ha, ha, no, I just...
我跌倒了
I fell down.
倒在别人嘴唇上？
On someone's lips?
你的草莓从哪来的？
Where'd you get the hickey?
- 大概是派对或…    - 什么派对？
- You know, a party or...     - What party?
其实不太算派对 只是一群人聚在一起
Well, it wasn't a party so much as a... A gathering of people.
有食物和音乐和…
With food and music and...
和乐团
And the band.
你们跟混混与自大狂一起参加派对？
You partied with Hootie and the Blowfish?
对 显然史提夫和混混很熟
Yes. Apparently, Stevie and Hootie are like this.
谁给你那草莓的？
Who gave you that hickey?
应该是其中一个自大狂种的
That would be the work of a Blowfish.
我不敢相信…
I can't believe it. I can't believe this.
我们只是呆坐在家 试着猜乔伊比几根手指
We're just sitting at home, trying to guess Joey's fingers...
你们则在外面狂欢 玩得很开心
and you guys are out, like, partying and having fun and all:
"自大狂 来吸我的脖子"
"Hey, Blowfish, suck on my neck."
听着 别怪我们 你们原本可以在场
Hey, look, don't blame us. You guys could've been there.
干嘛？参与你的穷朋友施舍计划？
Oh, what? As part of your Poor Friends Outreach program?
太好了 公司打来的
Oh, great. It's work.
我不知道该说什么 很遗憾我们赚得比你们多
Look, I don't know what to say. I'm sorry that we make more than you.
但我们不打算觉得愧咎 我们是辛苦工作得到的
But we're not gonna feel guilty about it. We work really hard for it.
那我们没辛苦工作吗？
And we don't work hard?
对 我是摩妮卡 有人呼叫我
Yeah, hi, it's Monica. I got a page.
我只是说 有时我们想做会比较花钱的事
I'm just saying that sometimes we like to do stuff that costs a little more.
- 你觉得我们成了你的绊脚石   - 对
- Oh, and you feel like we hold you back.     - Yes.
不对
No.
里昂 等一下 大家安静
Leon, wait. Shh! Guys.
等等 我不了解
Wait, I don't understand.
那些牛排只是肉商的礼物
Those steaks were just a gift from the meat vendor.
那不是回扣
That was not a kickback.
拜托 我会补回去 我们就能忘掉这整件事
Come on, I'll just replace them and we can forget the whole thing.
什么企业政策？
What corporate policy?
是
Yeah.
好的
Okay.
我刚刚被开除了
I just got fired.
这是你的帐单 四点一二元
Here's your check. That'll be 4.12.
我来付
Let me get that.
你有五元吗？
You got 5 bucks?
哔声要来了 你知道该怎么做
Here comes the beep. You know what to do.
嗨 是我
Hi, it's me.
听着 巴伯 我也许太过分了
Listen, Bob, I'm probably way out of line here.
毕竟已经过了三年 你可能正在跟别人交拄
I mean, it has been three years, and you're probably seeing someone else now...
但是假如我们能共度一晚 当作看在往日情分上
but if we could just have one night together, just for old time's sake...
火热 热情 狂野的一晚…
One hot, steamy, wild night...